[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Hey! Is anyone there?
Anyone there? Hey!
Shut up!
Who are you? Let me out!
Who are you? Why am I here? Hey!
It's no use.
And who are you?
I tried before you woke up.
They won't open the door.
Why kidnap me?
Why are we at sea?
It's over.
Jung found out. I'm doomed.
Jung? You mean my boss?
What did he find out?
Do you work for Jung too?
I'm his accountant.
You got some nerve.
I'm just his driver.
How could I refuse?
What are you talking about?
An accountant for a large construction company.
How'd you make time to sleep with his wife?
Sleep with his… How could I possibly do that?
Then why are you here?
Jung can't possibly suspect me.
I've only seen his wife twice.
Why explain this to me?
You're locked up here, just like me.
Unsure if we'll be tossed into the sea.
He must want to silence me.
He thought I leaked that he was cooking the books.
Money laundering?
Jung does that for many politicians and tycoons.
Doesn't everyone know?
Someone must have set me up.
If I'd wanted to rat him out, I would've long ago!
If you left any of that evidence with someone close to you,
perhaps they could expose him after we're dead
in retaliation.
My wife might see the ledgers in my study.
Given who she is, she would never…
She wouldn't dare do anything.
My son just started junior high school.
I…
The study?
You're doing the dirty part next time.
Hey, thanks for your cooperation.
You tricked me!
Someone will make a copy of those ledgers in your study.
That will be me.
Don't worry. You and your family will be fine.
There's food and drinks. Help yourself.
But if you want to stop us…
Think about how you'll explain it to Jung.
My wife might see the ledgers in my study.
Given who she is, she would never…
We're on our way to get the ledgers.
No news is good news.
Hurry back after you get them.
Chairman's got a new task for you.
Can we stop working for the police?
It makes us seem like the police.
How could we turn down the head of the National Police Agency?
If you have complaints, talk to the chairman.
THE FIXERS
THE SWAMP EEL
Come on.
Get in the zone!
Go big or go home!
Place big bets if you want deep pockets.
-Come on! -Okay.
Here.
No more bets.
Big!
-Small. -Big.
Come on!
Here it goes!
Triple takes it all.
The triple takes it all. Say "uncle," you all.
Okay. Quit gambling today.
What are you doing here? Continue.
Want to leave after winning?
Sorry. Got dinner with my pretty wife.
Who are you kidding?
Yours is waiting for you too, damn it.
I have no wife today. Continue.
Continue.
Wait, hold on.
Goddamn it.
What? Running off on us?
Do not go gentle into that good night.
Everything will turn out right. Hurry.
Hey, Milky.
What the heck?
Oh, Pond Loach.
My goodness.
-Business is good. -Milky.
I'm Swamp Eel.
-I'll make it for you. -Make, my ass.
You're two months late on your protection money.
Well, Milky…
Business hasn't been great lately.
How about this?
Let's go another round?
Yeah, let's go again!
Come on.
That much?
-All in? -All in on big.
Bet on big!
Okay, no more bets.
No regrets.
Big!
Show it!
Show it.
What's up? Too scared to reveal it?
Who's afraid?
Here it goes!
Fuck you! Cheater!
No.
Milky, listen to me.
Maybe the fan was too strong. It shifted the dice.
I didn't cheat.
Keep spouting nonsense.
I know your greatest asset
is this golden index finger.
Your former boss got a 30-million-dollar policy on it.
You see what I'm saying now?
Fine.
I'll pay.
Move.
Move aside.
Pay, your ass!
Chase him!
Granny, gotta go!
-Collectors again? -No!
Stop!
-You're fine. -Stop!
Help me!
Fuck. Let's go.
Where is he? Fuck!
Fuck you. Stop!
Stop!
Come on.
Shit, he's climbing!
-This monkey! -Damn it!
Fuck.
Fuck! Still running?
-Hello? -Dad, we're screwed.
I know that.
I don't mean you.
It's Mom.
Over there.
You fucking traitor.
-Stop! -Stop! Fuck!
Fuck! Stop!
Fuck, you damn old ape! Motherfucker!
Stop!
-What's with the chase? -Don't let me catch you!
Need this!
Hey, my swamp eel!
Motherfucker.
Fuck!
So many of you? Not down there!
Fuck you!
Get out!
Stop, motherfucker!
Stop fighting!
Beat him!
Move it!
Come on!
Fuck! Chase!
Tell us if there's a problem.
Bye.
Hey! Officer.
-Are you okay? -Can I get a ride home?
-What's wrong? -So I have diabetes.
I left my insulin syringe at home.
So, yes?
You need an ambulance?
No. It's faster if you drive me.
Okay. Come on. Watch out.
Ask him for his address. We'll take him home.
Come on.
I am the captain of my soul. The police protect the people.
Bud, what's going on? Where's your mom?
Live streaming.
-Why? Isn't she in trouble? -See for yourself.
He told me to buy some kind of cryptocurrency.
It went up over 100 times.
Over 100 times!
He said the company was launching a new coin
that would surge and was a must-buy.
So I bought it. Look.
In just half a month…
-12%. It went up 12%! -Seriously?
My husband often says,
"Press your wins and go for broke."
-So I had to buy more, right? -Do I?
-I guess? -Do I?
Hey, own what you said, all right?
I wanted to cash out. But guess what?
The company said it was under investigation. Look.
I can't get any of my money back!
It's fine. It's just five million.
Shipping next month. Promise.
Delivered fresh to your door.
Gosh, when has Wonder Wendy ever lied to you?
Didn't you say it was an investment?
-Report it to the police. -I already did.
They said I might never get it back.
Hold up.
I'm a victim.
You should be comforting, not scolding me.
I don't mind that you play mah-jongg all day.
But you got scammed. Why wouldn't I scold you?
I should be the one talking.
You go out every day and come home all dirty.
You might have a mistress.
I say you're obsessed with money.
Scammers love people like you.
Felix Chiang.
Be honest with yourself.
In all the time we've been married,
have I ever had an easy day?
Still, I raised our child and helped bring in extra money.
This family would've collapsed otherwise.
So now it's my problem?
-My fault? -No.
I…
I just want to earn a little more money.
All right.
We can earn that money back.
I'll take care of it.
Hey.
That was a lot. How will you manage?
Please, who do you think I am?
This amount used to be nothing to me, okay?
By the way, where's the money from?
I just…
used our house as collateral and borrowed that in your name.
You're so smart.
You're incredible!
CHIU CHA TEMPLE
Ma'am.
Are you seeking guidance?
CONSULTATION FORM, CHAO MING-CHENG
Please draw a fortune stick.
No need for divination blocks.
FANG CHIAO-HUI
The fortune slip reads,
"Let he who tied the bell on the tiger take it off."
If Mr. Chao runs into any trouble,
tell him to handle it himself.
How did it go?
They want you to go there in person.
CHING HE TEMPLE
This way, please.
CHAO MING-CHENG
Mr. Chao.
Are you in trouble?
Please come with me.
TAI SUI HALL
I am Thackery Huang, the chairman of Ching He.
What can I do for you, Mr. Chao?
As Attorney Chao Ming-cheng is seeking reelection to the legislature,
news broke of his son's drug possession.
The leaked video…
MING-CHENG'S SON PASSED OUT WITH SUSPECTED DRUGS
What do you think of this?
Party leaders will likely shift their support to Lu Shu-jung
and force Chao to withdraw.
Then I shall congratulate you.
Lu Shu-jung is a conservative within the party.
If she is elected, it will help you become mayor.
-It's the minister. -Hello, sir.
MING YOUNG PARTY FUNDRAISER
Sir, many note that you are still active in retirement.
If your eldest son becomes mayor,
will he be a puppet mayor?
What's your response?
Let's keep the focus on today's fundraiser.
Sir, please wait and take a photo.
Louis.
Join us.
-Come. -Who is this young man?
-The second son of the Hsuehs? -No, that's impossible.
Doesn't he have only one son? I've never seen him before.
Stand in the middle.
Yung?
-What's up? -Just warning you.
Milky is telling people that you rig your games.
I heard your family got scammed for five million dollars.
How did you know?
Didn't your wife cry in front of the world?
The news is all over. What are your plans now?
If that venue is no good anymore, I'll go somewhere else.
I'll pay off the debts before I die
and make a little more for my wife and son.
I have a gig that pays quick cash.
Someone owes my friend money.
You just have to flash a gun as a warning.
I don't touch guns anymore.
You were such a badass. If you return--
I wandered lonely as a cloud. Cut the crap and spit it out.
That was so long ago, all right?
I called you 'cause I knew you wouldn't pull the trigger.
300,000 dollars. No need to shoot. Just flash a gun.
Well?
Didn't I tell you already? I don't touch guns anymore.
Think about it. I'll call you again.
Find someone else.
Dad, what are you looking for?
You scared me to death.
Have you seen a tin box with a floral pattern?
No. Why are you looking for that?
Hey, listen.
Earn big and support your mom. Okay? Don't be like me.
Don't underestimate her. She'll earn it all back by live streaming.
How was she?
She was on the phone with Auntie.
"Gosh, how could I be so stupid and sell the house?"
Nothing you haven't heard before.
Found it.
-What's inside? -Nothing.
Aren't midterms tomorrow? Go study.
Okay.
Bud.
Good luck.
Don't worry, bud.
-Hello? -Hello?
So?
Stop overthinking. It's decided.
I'll send you the address.
Goddamn it.
Mr. Hung, long time no see.
Long time no see.
This is Tristan, my son.
Here. This is Minister Wang.
This is Minister Chen.
-Hello. -Nice to meet you.
Please look after this young man.
He's promising.
-Hey, hello. -Hello.
-Sir, long time no see. -I should call you Legislator Lu now.
Oh, no.
But the decision on this seat could indeed come early tonight.
I'm sure you have many plans for when you become a legislator.
Don't worry.
I will personally oversee the Hsin Nan redevelopment project.
It will all go smoothly.
One vodka martini.
Make it a double.
I don't need to be sober for this.
What's your drink?
Orange juice.
You don't need alcohol for such an event?
I can't drink. I'm working.
Make it two.
All the more reason to drink.
Louis Hsueh. Hello.
Are you Mr. Hsueh's son?
Hello. I'm Viki, Lu Shu-jung's aide.
I haven't seen you much at events like this.
My dad rarely brings me to these occasions.
I'm not a socializer.
I get it.
Sorry.
-Sorry. Your pants. -It's okay.
How will you compensate me?
Why don't we exchange our numbers?
Excuse me.
I didn't expect you to be so bold.
There are many people downstairs.
You've done this before.
What do you mean?
I can't believe a PhD graduate
had to hook up with her boss's husband
to become an assistant.
Where did you get that photo?
I'm the one asking now.
What do you want?
Chao Ming-cheng's son's drug case.
Did you hire someone to frame him?
I don't know what you're saying.
Do you think I should post these photos online
or send them to the press downstairs?
Are you backing me into a corner?
I don't have to post them.
I only want to know who you hired.
Lu Shu-jung's husband hired Noods.
In exchange for what?
When Lu Shu-jung becomes a legislator,
his business won't be investigated.
Is Lu Shu-jung that resourceful?
Of course not.
When she succeeds,
I'll pay someone to anonymously report him for drug dealing and kidnapping.
She just has to deny everything.
When she succeeds,
I'll pay someone to anonymously report him for drug dealing and kidnapping.
If you don't tell anyone what happened here,
you and these photos will remain safe.
As Attorney Chao Ming-cheng is seeking reelection to the legislature,
news broke that his son was in possession of drugs.
The leaked video clearly shows unidentified powder around him.
Chao, who spoke of the rule of law and clean governance--
Hey.
Are you going in?
How come it's a pig farm?
It's a cover for Noods's business that packages drugs.
Something feels wrong.
What? Have you lost your guts after being away for so long?
Don't worry. Nobody knows you're there.
All right.
Noods.
Is it worth risking your life for them?
Hey, how much did they pay you?
Don't know what you mean. Shoot me if you dare.
It's not about the money.
Won't talk, huh?
Of course not.
When she succeeds,
I'll pay someone to anonymously report him for drug dealing and kidnapping.
She just has to deny everything.
They used you. Now they're throwing you under the bus.
Fuck, you can't trust a politician's word.
What do you want?
Give me the evidence that Mr. Chao's son was framed,
and I guarantee you'll get out of this safe and sound.
You'll get paid too.
It's in the pigsty outside.
Buddy.
I didn't mean to shoot you.
I really didn't see anything.
You don't work for Noods?
No.
I was sent here to collect a debt from him.
Bring me the bag over there.
GOLD
-Hello? -Did you get it?
I got shot.
Where are you? I'm coming.
No need.
There's no time.
I'll send the file to you first. Hold on.
Motherfucker.
I got the video, but the phone is broken. I can't send it to you.
Someone's with you?
Hello?
The client goes on stage in 30 minutes.
Have you found the evidence yet?
Look someone up for me. I'll send you a photo.
FELIX CHIANG, SWAMP EEL, 55 YEARS OLD
Put me on speaker.
Felix Chiang.
Who are you?
Bring the phone in 20 minutes. Kuang He Road Garage, top floor.
Hand it over to a red sports car.
Why should I do this for you?
Howie Chiang.
Your son's got a nice name.
Attends Ping Cheng Junior High.
Top 30 at school.
How did you know?
What do you want?
Twenty minutes.
Bring the phone in 20 minutes.
You and your family will be safe.
Otherwise, you'll find out.
-Motherfucker. -Thank you.
Damn it.
Hey, is that your car? Quick.
Mr. Chao.
You'll be on stage in ten minutes. Are you ready?
Don't be so cocky.
I'll settle the score with you one day.
Sure. I'll wait.
Sir, it's time to get ready.
The host will go over the rundown.
-I can't reach Noods. -How can that be?
GPS shows it's nearing the venue.
Take care of this no matter what.
BREAD AND CAKES
Hurry up.
Did you come from the pigsty?
Isn't that obvious?
-Stand back and wait. -Hold up.
I delivered it. Can I go now?
Wait. Let me check it first.
Hurry up.
Bring the phone to Chao Ming-cheng at the fundraiser next door.
Why should I? Deliver it yourself.
Ridiculous.
Top 30 at school.
What a pity it would be to lose him.
It's him. Get him!
Bastard! Stop!
Come back!
-Fuck! -Come back!
Stop!
If you stop, I stop!
-Stop! -Fuck!
MING YOUNG PARTY
Hello, everyone.
I am Chao Ming-cheng.
Thank you for all your support.
Since entering politics,
I've worked diligently every day to serve the people.
I have never done anything against my conscience.
However, now that I'm older,
my mind has changed.
All right. Enough.
Where's the stuff for Chao Ming-cheng?
Didn't I already tell you?
It's in the phone.
Are you playing dumb?
There are only porn videos.
Fuck.
He likes watching porn that much?
How would I know?
Damn, still playing dumb with me? Beat him up!
CHING HE TEMPLE
Such a good runner.
Fuck.
Run again.
Over the years,
I have devoted all my time to work…
and neglected my family.
After careful consideration,
-I formally announce-- -Sir.
I formally announce
that I won't quit the race.
I have proof that my son was falsely accused!
These rumors won't defeat me!
I'll continue to serve the people.
I won't back down!
This isn't convincing. Sprinkle more. Get some powder on him.
MISSION COMPLETE
Get out!
You tricked me! Get out!
How did you escape that?
Fuck! I used to take on over a dozen men.
They're nothing!
Get in. I'll treat you to a snack.
Fuck you!
Don't let me see you again.
Fixer Shadow was taken in for treatment.
The surveillance footage nearby has been taken care of.
Then we can ask Mr. Chao to make a donation.
Okay.
You may be interested in one more thing.
EARTH
ARCANE
TERRA
PRIMORDIUM
The surge has sent the crypto market into euphoria.
The CEO of Yuan Tao, a major local crypto platform,
made a surprising comment in an interview.
He believes this is just the beginning of the surge.
The real show is only getting started.
Where the heck have you been?
You weren't answering your phone.
I had something to handle at the gambling house.
Why aren't you sleeping in bed?
I was waiting for you.
Gosh. What happened? Your face is injured.
Some asshole flashed their headlights, and I fell.
Go to sleep.
-Be more careful. -Okay.
…not give in under any pressure.
He will continue to fight for justice for the people.
An incident at a nearby hospital was reported after the press conference.
Multiple mobsters were injured and taken to the hospital…
Attorney Chao Ming-cheng stressed that he would not give in
under any pressure.
He will continue to fight for justice for the people.
An incident at a nearby hospital was reported after the press conference.
Multiple mobsters were injured and taken to the hospital…
Gosh, you scared me.
Did you have a nightmare?
What were you so busy with last night?
San He, the largest local gang…
You came back injured and kept switching to the news channel.
To prevent any accidents, the police deployed over 100 officers…
-Hello? -Well? Did you scare the life out of him?
I'll start with this.
I didn't kill Noods. Someone else did.
What?
Noods is dead?
-You didn't know? -Damn it!
I thought you never shoot.
Listen, I didn't ask you to kill him.
-Don't call me again. -I told you. It wasn't me.
Fuck!
…in the spotlight.
In a major move today, he unveiled a municipal study on traffic congestion…
TAI SUI HALL
Subtitle translation by: Hannah Liu